<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Ad -->
    <string name="ad_attribution">Ad</string>
    
    <!-- Help Dialog -->
    <string name="user_manual_title">User Manual</string>
    <string name="close_content_description">Close</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    
    <!-- Help Pages -->
    <string name="help_page_1_title">Thank you for using PDF Ansimi</string>
    <string name="help_page_1_content">PDF Ansimi is an app that allows you to safely redact sensitive information in PDF documents.\n\nKey Features:\n• Load PDF files\n• Mask text and image areas\n• Save redacted PDF\n\nLearn how to use the app through this guide.</string>
    
    <string name="help_page_2_title">1. Opening a PDF File</string>
    <string name="help_page_2_content">To open a PDF file:\n\n1. Tap the \'+\' button at the bottom right of the home screen.\n2. Select a PDF file from your device.\n3. Once loaded, you will be taken to the editor screen.\n\nRecently worked projects are displayed as a list on the home screen.</string>
    
    <string name="help_page_3_title">2. Masking Areas</string>
    <string name="help_page_3_content">First, click the masking toggle button at the bottom.\n\nTo redact sensitive information:\n\n1. Touch the area you want to hide on the PDF page.\n2. Drag your finger to draw the masking area.\n3. When you release your finger, the area will be covered in black.\n\nYou can mask multiple areas, and each area is managed individually.\n\nWhen masking is complete, click the toggle button again to exit masking mode.</string>
    
    <string name="help_page_4_title">3. Page Navigation</string>
    <string name="help_page_4_content">To navigate through a multi-page PDF:\n\n• Check the page number at the bottom of the screen.\n• Use the left/right arrow buttons to move to the previous/next page.\n• You can perform masking operations independently on each page.</string>
    
    <string name="help_page_5_title">4. Saving PDF</string>
    <string name="help_page_5_content">After completing the masking work:\n\n1. Tap the save button at the top.\n2. The redacted PDF will be saved to your device.\n3. You can check the save location through the system notification.\n\nThe original file will not be modified, and it will be saved as a new file.\n\n※ PDF file size cannot exceed 50MB.</string>
    
    <string name="help_page_6_title">Need Help?</string>
    <string name="help_page_6_content">If you need additional support:\n\n• Check the version information in the app info.\n• If you encounter problems, try restarting the app.\n• To delete a project, tap the trash icon on the home screen.\n\nFor inquiries, please contact voll1212@gmail.com.\n\nThank you for using PDF Redactor!</string>
    
    <!-- Exit Confirmation Dialog -->
    <string name="exit_dialog_title">Do you want to exit the app?</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_yes">Exit</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_no">Cancel</string>
    <string name="exit_dialog_review">Leave a Review</string>
</resources>
